Hey, what's up everybody? Today I want
to talk about AI agents and particularly
the new version of AI agents, AI skills
and how instead of building big massive
AI agent workflows, we can use automated
AI agent tools that actually do work for
us. I've been doing this all week. My
agents have been going to work. I found
that agents was a very difficult thing
to figure out for a while and now what
it's happening is is that whole agent
workflow is changing. The world of
agents is actually changed over the last
couple of weeks as we have discovered
with claude code and all these different
tools that are out there. But what is an
AI agent? That's one of the first places
I want to start with you here.
Particularly an AI agent is where you
have AI and many of us are used to
things like chat GPT or Claude or Gemini
or maybe you use Perplexity or something
like that. And the agent
version is where it can do stuff for
you. So instead of it being a chatbot
that you're chatting with and you're
like, "Okay,
what's a recipe for this?" or you're
asking it some kind of information, you
actually tell an agent to go do
something. So, the AI
is able to look
and
act because it's based on some kind of
knowledge about how to do it. And now
what we've had is recently there have
been major advances with what Claude has
launched. They recently launched this
past week Claude Coowwork,
which is a general AI agent that can do
work for you. One of the easiest general
AI agents that's out there to use. And
the the cheapest to find is going to be
what's called it's it's through a
platform called Manis. And so the reason
why I like Manis is because anybody can
use it. They can sign up for an account
and they can ask the agent to do just
about anything for them. Like I was I
was able to for some of my clients, I
was able to actually create
a landing page and be able to look at a
landing page for an offer that she was
creating and different versions of this
landing page right here with this agent.
I was able to give it instructions to go
out there and do various things for me
and build these things with Manis.
Another AI agent it's is lovable.dev.
We've been using this recently.
Lovable.dev is really cool because it
can build landing pages for businesses.
You know, we we we're playing around
with a a business here for a handyman
business right here. We we have
um an agent. This is one for a dog
grooming company right here. Uh dog
grooming. And what the what the agent
did was we told it what kind of site we
want to build, what kind of text we want
to put in there, and the agent built
everything for us. And so no longer
instead of you having to go out there
and create it all yourself, the agent
can go do a lot of the work for you.
Now, one of the more advanced ways that
agents work are like tools like Claude
Code and particularly
Claude Co-work, which is the new one
that came out for non-technical people
to use. If you're not a coder or
developer, I've been having a lot of fun
with my agents. I've been developing
various apps. I I created a chatbot app,
a a transcript app, a scheduler app all
this week, uh, which is awesome, and
even a a healthcare app for one of our
clients. But Claude Co-work, what it
does is it can connect to your computer
and it can do work, whether it be in
your browser, it can organize your
desktop files for you. And the idea is
it's a robot. It's a robotic way of
actually doing work for you. the the
robot is programmed with certain
functions that it can then go out and
do. So, here's what I love. Claude
Co-work and Manis particularly, I would
say Manis is probably one of the easiest
agents, a general agent that you can
dive into is is an incredible one right
here. Um, it can it can even control
your web browser right here inside of
Manis on your computer. You can use it
through their app. Um, oh, there's an
agent inside of uh this site called
replet.com that can build apps for you
as well. There's an agent. You tell it
what app you want to build. The agent
goes out and it figures out how to build
it for you. So again, the idea of agents
is this is it takes the concept of a
robot that can do stuff and it goes in
and it just figures it out. It figures
out how to do those things based on
parameters that you're able to give it.
Some agents exist inside of chat GPT
even. They have a chat GPT agent that's
built inside of chat GPT. They have a
coding agent. They have a general agent
right here under agent mode. What can it
do for you and things like that. And so
these are all really, really cool things
that exist that are out there. But how
can we apply them in our business? Well,
you could have it build you a website.
You can have it make an app for you. But
you could also learn about creating
custom GPTs. And this is one of the
really cool ways that I think a lot of
people can use agents is with custom
GPTs inside of chat GPT. They can go in
and they can create a custom GPT based
on any topic. You can go here under chat
GPT/GPTs
and find these based on different topics
and look them up. whether it be a
copywriting GPT, whether it be a
Facebook ads GPT. And the idea is that
it can create ads for you. It can write
copy. It can generate workflows and
things like that. But you can also
create your own GPT by clicking there's
a create button on this screen.
And they have a little agent right here,
the GPT agent builder. as far as what it
is. What are some ideas for agent GPTs
that you could make? I could actually
just ask it that to give me some ideas
for what it could make, which is really
pretty cool.
Uh, a focus coach, a meeting summarizer,
a brand voice builder,
uh, script companion, a a
learning guide. Let let's say um kids TV
shows
learning guide. How to translate
episodes of kids shows into learning
lessons for homeschooling.
Boom. Like that right there is something
that I could use right now. I have a I
have a son who is um three years old. He
watches different TV shows and stuff
like that. How could I then translate
certain lessons from certain show
episodes into homeschooling type
lessons? I think that would be really
cool. And so the the GPT agent can
actually go out there and create that
for me. It's going to go out there and
it's going to actually build itself some
custom instructions. So again, that's
what an agent is, is it has the chatbot
and then it's combined with some kind of
information
and parameters
of how it should act and respond.
Now, these agents are turning into these
more autonomous agents. Uh, Claude Code
is a great example of an autonomous
agent. You can give it a problem with
your app that you're building and it
will literally sit there for an hour and
solve it and fix it in the background
while you have five other agents doing
other things for you. Imagine the
possibility of that. I'm not a software
developer and yet I've been able to
generate and build different software
that actually works and actually
functions and actually creates these
amazing apps that I'm able to use right
here on my computer which is awesome
using tools like uh cloud code uh I
created crack chat and all these it's a
chatbot it's things like that and so
that's what agents are really good at
but the way that most people are going
to use agents again is like lovable
where it can build you out a whole
website based on a concept or or a
landing page. Lovable is very easy to
log into and create an account with and
start using to create custom landing
pages.
Um or Manis Manis can go out there and
it can actually like do different work
and research. like I had it research the
best way to build a certain website that
then I was able to feed into lovable. It
was able to go out there and do all this
research for me. Um, it was able to come
up with how to create certain skills for
claude code and how to do things like
that. I was able to outline a marketing
plan for a handyman business. I was able
to come up with a flow for how to build
out ads campaigns and how to I was able
to also have it do work where it went
into Aweber, an email software, and
extracted all of these emails and it
created an email writing system prompt
for us that could create an agent bot
that could then write emails inside of
software for us using these different
techniques and tools. And so again,
whether it be something like
an agent chatbot like this
sounds good, like a GPT builder or
whether it be something like Manis that
can actually go into your websites. It
can go into your email software,
schedule emails, write emails for you,
do all this, do lots of research. I had
it rewrite my whole uh marketing
campaign for a new funnel that I was
creating right here last week, which is
awesome. Um uh I had the agent go in and
actually write an entire ebook based on
transcripts, hours and hours of raw
transcripts. We had it translate into a
full ebook that then what we're doing is
we're editing, we're adding pictures to
and all of that. So, it was able to save
us just weeks and weeks and weeks of
time with these agents that are going
and doing this type of work. Okay. And
so, those are some different tools.
Again, like I'd recommend Manis, um,
Claude Co-work for most people. You need
a Claude Max account to use it, which is
about 100 bucks a month. Um, Lovable.
Lovable and Manis, you can use them.
There's a free version. There's a about
a $20 a month version that you can use
to play around with.
Um, agents come in all different shapes
and sizes. There's these app building
agents that that do this. But here's the
interesting thing is that when it comes
to agents, we've barely scratched the
surface as far as what agents could
really do for us in our businesses. And
I want to ask Claude Opus this
in the future with the idea of
autonomous agents like Claude code and
even features like claude skills.
Let me tell you about claude skills.
Claude skills are these actually things
you create many documents with multiple
layers of how it it actually functions
and Claude will actually write it for
you to create these autonomous agents
that can do multiple layers of work
using Claude skills to be able to do
them which is amazing. We can say
brainstorm new unique ways
that agents might exist and help us do
work in the future that don't exist
already. Let's ask Claude this to really
come up with these ideas, some novel
autonomous agent ideas, these robot
ideas. is you know Elon Musk is creating
these these Tesla Optimus robots
as a part of his vision and these are
autonomous robots that actually can move
around. I have a Tesla car that
autonomously can drive itself by itself
and do all these different things and
it's amazing. But for the average
person, you know, maybe we're not quite
there yet with everything. But what we
do have is we have these different tools
that are on our computer. So right here,
ambient agents instead of ones you
summon, they passively observe what you
do and build context maps. They not just
acting, but understanding that we're on
the cusp of things like that with things
like claw code and clawed co-work. Uh
adversarial partner agents whose
explicit job is to argue against your
plans, find holes in stress test
assumptions. That's kind of cool. Agent
swarms with emergent specializations.
This is again like a coding agent or a
writing agent that can develop multiple
layers. If you were writing a book, you
could develop all your characters with
an agent and it could do these different
things. Uh temporal agents, a model of
you six months from now and six months
ago and based on your trajectory could
simulate certain things. Relationship
aware agents, they understand your
social graph and ways that you could
change the way your social dynamic is. a
dream agent. How to take your half-baked
ideas and develop them into something
useful. Negotiation agents,
forgetting agents, their job is to
remove information from your systems.
Embodied process agents. A new client
onboarding agent lives inside the
workflow. Agents only activate when
certain conditions are met. So again,
this can make your head kind of explode,
this whole idea about agents and things
like that. But here's the beautiful
thing about it. What's happening is
different developers and people like
myself and things like that, we're
creating tools for you that you can use
that do things that are amazing things
every single day. Right now, where
agents exist right now is not where
they're always going to exist. And so in
the future, who knows what's possible?
Certain things that can come together in
ways that that robots start working
autonomously in all of our systems.
That's really AI really actually is a a
gateway to robotics inside of our lives
and all those different things and
pre-programmed
workflows and functionalities.
You can do a ton of things with agents.
The way that I use it, I set up my
marketing agents to come up with
different concepts and things that I do.
I want to I want to create an agent off
of a video like this that could create
all my social media posts, multiple
videos, graphics, memes, things that I
could post and share with people off of
just one piece of video content. And
that's an agent that I'd actually like
to build. I'd like to actually take the
transcript of this and feed it into an
agent builder and actually build some
kind of a tool that could do that for me
based on my individual
um details that I feed into it.
which is an awesome thing that I'd love
to be able to do that I' I want to be
able to build and something that I am
building right now. And so what are ways
that you could use AI agents to take
your work and save you time, effort,
energy, the amount of time, effort, and
energy that you put into brainstorming
and coming up with ideas and trying to
solve problems, the agent can start to
do it for you. And that's where we're
headed and things like that. Inside of
my wealthy coach academy, I'm teaching
my clients right now how to use AI
agents and how to build them and how to
not lose your voice, not lose your
autonomy. See, here's the idea is you
could have an army of agents that work
for you like they are employees that are
doing different work for you. And
[snorts] that's one of the beautiful
things and ways that agents work is you
have these virtual
employees actually doing the work for
you and creating outputs that are just
incredible that are just out of this
world. And so I would I would just
encourage you go out there, think about
the different ways that we can use
these. Start using some of them. They're
not hard to use. They they work just
like chat GPT, but they can do stuff for
you. And that's the difference between
the promise of agents is things like
that. We have this um this GPT that I
was creating over here. I want to just
test it out while we're on the screen
here. It's its agent is actually
building the GPT for us right here. It's
creating this out that we can use to be
able to do different things and stuff
like that with it.
And so here's our custom GPT for kids
shows in episode two of season one of
Superkitties.
Come up with ideas for homeschool.
And the agent can actually go to work by
looking on the web and actually coming
up with how this might work together.
Let's imagine episode one, super sleuth
science. Solve mysteries like the
superkitties. Set up a mystery in your
room. Who took down the missing button?
Leave clues. Teach logic and observation
skills,
creativity.
And so this is again a way that you
could build out agents that can help you
do certain things. Like I built one for
writing Facebook ads and things like
that. And the idea was that it was able
to
write ads based on a landing page that
we actually put in there to be able to
create the types of things that we want
to create
in our business. And so what it was able
to do is it was able to go out there and
it was able to
by coming up with what the ad says,
here's the landing page, here's the
sales copy. It was able to do that.
Inside of my Wealthy Coach Academy
program, I'm showing business owners
every single day how to implement these
in their business, how to get results,
and how to scale and produce the kind of
income that they want to produce,
whether it be six figures, seven
figures, and beyond. I'd love to help
you inside of my Wealthy Coach Academy
program to get incredible results in
your business. We'll talk soon,
everybody. Have a good one.